VERONICA BERGSTRÖM

ABOUT

"Veronica has shown many valuable traits as a developer. She is **curious**, **thorough**, and has **great problem-solving skills**. She also impressed me with her ability to **work independently**, far more than I initially expected. Socially, she has been **a joy to work with**, happy, social, and communicative, which has greatly contributed to a positive and collaborative work environment."

/Amanda Olsson Front End Developer and mentor, Oneflow AB

LANGUAGES

English Proficient •••••

Swedish Native •••••

FIND ME ONLINE



https://www.linkedin.com/in/veronic a-b-a863b567/

GitHub

https://github.com/innoVeraz

TRAINING / COURSES

Web Development Astar 2021

Business Economics Astar 2021

Math

NTI School 2020

Full Stack Developer

📞 +46725397833 🔘 v.bergstrom.dev@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/veronica-b-a863b567/

SKILLS

React · Next.js · TypeScript · JavaScript · Redux · Zustand · HTML · API Development ·

RESTful API Development · Node.js · Authentication & Authorization · CSS · Sass · Tailwind ·

Socket.io · framer-motion

GraphQL · Postgres · MongoDB · SQL · NoSQL · Docker · Prisma · Jest · Cypress · E2E ·

In learning (Python)

Jira - CI/CD - Fly.io - GitLab - Git

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

10/2023 - 05/2024

Stockholm

Oneflow AB

· React, Redux, Sass, Atlassian Bamboo, Jira.

- · Became TypeScript Pioneer.
- · Migrated components from flow to TypeScript.
- · Collaborated on the integration of a self-upgrade feature.
- · Developed reusable components.
- · Demonstrated skills in bug solving.
- Transformed class components into functional using refactoring methods.
- · SaaS product.

Customer Success Manager

08/2016 - 01/2020

Stockholm

Afound

• Led start-up activities and project management for Afound marketplace launch.

- Onboarded and established relationships with our partners and sellers.
- Developed comprehensive system requirements and workflow documentation.
- Performed extensive testing to validate the functionality of our systems and feature implementations.

Flow Manager

Fyndiq AB

Stockholm

08/2012 - 04/2016

- Assisted in start-up projects.
- Established system requirements to guide development and testing processes.
- Collaborated with legal partners to create comprehensive educational material.
- · Delegated and prioritized tasks on a daily basis.
- · Managed products in our PIM and supported our sellers.

EDUCATION

Front End Developer

08/2022 - 06/2024

Medieinstitutet AB

Stockholm

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- · Testing (e2e, unit)
- HTML
- CSS/Sass
- UX-Design
- Work methods for developers
- Agile work methods
- SQL/NoSQL